Guide to the Yale Law School Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Law School student records
1903-1998
RU 263
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
181.5
(186 boxes)
The records consist of student transcripts maintained by the Yale Law School registrar.
Yale Law School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26-F (YRG 26-F), Student records of the Yale Law School.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student transcripts maintained by the Yale Law School registrar.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Law students; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Students
- Student transcripts [microfilm], circa 1930-1989; Accession 1981-A-016
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  - 1930 grade cards through Merrill 1940 (J.D. ) (Reel 4)
  - 1940 Miller - 1950 Zucker (J.D.) (Reel 5)
  - 1951 Agger - 1957 Zimand (J.D.) (Reel 6)
  - 1958 Abernathy - 1964 Mimikes (J.D.) (Reel 7)
  - 1964 Nash - 1969 Zimines (J.D.) (Reel 8)
  - J.D.S., graduate students, non-graduate students, MSLS, 1930-1981 (Reel 12)
  - JSD, MSL, MSLS, LLM, 1981-1982 (Reel 13)
  - LLM and JSD, A-Z Transcripts, 1982-1983 (Reel 14)
  - Class of 1985 (Reel 16)
  - Class of 1986 (Reel 17)
  - Class of 1987 (Reel 18)
  - Class of 1988 (Reel 19)
  - Class of 1989 (Reel 20)
- Student records, circa 1903-1980; Accession 2002-A-171
  In accordance with university policy, the records are restricted until January 1, 2056.
- Student records, 1967-1998; Accession 2014-A-061
  Restricted until January 1, 2073
- Student records, 1971-1994; Accession 2014-A-082
- Student records, 1963-1997; Accession 2017-A-009
  In accordance with university policy, the records are restricted until January 1, 2073.